{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Java Script",
      "description": "Stuff on JS",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "Java Script Twow",
      "description": "more js",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "new",
      "description": "new",
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "When do javascripts execute?",
      "back": "immediately. as the page loads into the browser."
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "front": "how do you insert Javascript into a web page?",
      "back": "with the script tag:<script type=text/javascript">document.write("Hello World!");</script>"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "front": "Where do you put javascripts?;",
      "back": "in the head or body sections."
    },
    {
      "front": "What if you don't want the script to execute immediately upon loading a page?",
      "back": "then put it inside a function.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 37
    },
    {
      "front": "where do you place functions and why?",
      "back": "in the head section, this way they are all in one place, and they do not interfere with page content.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 38
    },
    {
      "front": "when should scripts be placed in the body?",
      "back": "when you want your script to be placed inside a function, or if your script should write page conten.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 39
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "front": "a edit",
      "back": "aa edit",
      "deckId": 5
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "front": "b edit",
      "back": "bb edit",
      "deckId": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "c",
      "back": "cc",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 42
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "front": "when should you use an external javascript?",
      "back": "when you want to run the same JavaScript on several pages, without having to write the same script on every page.",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "front": "how should an external javascript be referenced?",
      "back": "when you want to run the same JavaScript on several pages, without having to write the same script on every page.",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "front": "how should an external javascript be referenced?",
      "back": "<script type="text/javascript" src="xxx.js"></script>. name the file with a .js extension.",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 49
    },
    {
      "front": "can the external script contain the <script></script> tags?",
      "back": "No.",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 50
    },
    {
      "front": "how do you insert Javascript into a web page?",
      "back": "with the script tag:<script type="text/javascript">document.write("Hello World!");</script>",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 51
    }
  ]
}
